继   承   之   战
第 3 季  第 6 集
罗伊先生 我们希望可以
Mr. Roy, we'd like to move on
开始讨论非法支出的问题
to the matter of these illegal payments.
好吧
Fine.
我们不是已经讨论过了
I mean, we've done that but...
我们想具体了解一下
Specifically, your
你对事件的第一手了解
first-hand knowledge of what happened.
好 好 知道了
Yup. Yup. Got it.
我们希望你能
What we want you to explain to us
根据你的所见所闻
based on what you saw and heard
解释一下这些非法支出是如何进行 如何得到批复
is how these illegal payments were made were approved,
个中操作者有谁   -明白
and by whom. -Yup. Got it.
还有什么
What's next?
你不打算回答问题吗
You wanna answer the question?
我应该能行
I think I'm good.
好吧
Okay. Fine.
那些非法支出都是我批的  因为...
Well, I approved the illegal payments because
我爱性侵 也爱掩盖这一事实
I love sexual assault, and I love to cover it up.
怎么样  这样不行吗
How is that? Is that bad?
行了 我们可以收工了  -不行吗
-Okay. We can wrap up. -That's bad?
好了  我们回家后
I just will privately run the
私下过一下时间线吧
timeline at home, but, yeah.
我能行 我们都行的 对吧
I'm good, we're good, right?
很好 那就..
Good. And, yeah, just
谦卑一点 坦诚一点   -掩盖排练痕迹
humble  straightforward... -Hide the agenda.
不能有排练痕迹 -好
-No agenda. -Sure.
他们就是些政府职员
They're government employees. I mean,
能有多聪明呢
how smart can they be?
这话可不是我说的  只是你以为我想这么说  对吧
I'm not saying that. I'm saying what you think I think, right?
为了确保我们意见一致
And just so we're on the same page
就期望达到的目标而言  我想要
in terms of aims for me
免诉权  成立韦斯达特别工作组
the wish list goes immunity for yours truly taskforce for Waystar,
还有除掉我爸   -不要找我点歌[许愿]
my dad deaded.  -Well, I don't do requests
因为我不是 DJ
because I'm not a DJ
但我听到你的想法了  进来看看吧
but I hear you. Look, come in here.
他们正在拼接所有的文件
They're jigsawing all the papers.
文件大师们
Hey, paper people.
早上好
Good morning
韦斯达现在非常配合合作
You know, Waystar is now cooperating.
积极地提供了上十亿页的文件
Helpfully offering up one billion pages of documents
雇用了精英律师  前司法部人员
hiring white-shoe, former DOJ types
来进行内部检查  看上去无比严谨
to conduct an internal that looks super scrupulous
还主动安排员工  供司法部问讯
offering up employees for talks with DOJ
并拟定邮轮相关的工人安全协议
and worker safety protocols around cruises.
我们可以调整战略...但没法稳操胜券
We can adjust, but... This isn't a slam dunk here.
但.. 还有文件  不是吗
But... The papers. Yeah?
这.   -你一旦搬出那些落于
-I mean... -Once you pull everything out
其它司法管辖权
that falls under other jurisdictions,
海商法或是特权
or maritime law or is privileged,
或超出诉讼时效的东西...
or is outside the statute of limitations.
但如果从“反海外腐败法“切入  就能排除这些异议了吧
But an FCPA angle obviates those objections, right?
那些适用于“反海外腐败法“的东西
Well, the stuff that works
也不过是推理而来的
for Foreign Corrupt Practices Act is inferential.
韦斯达非常谨慎
Waystar was careful.
那你的意思就是这些文件都是狗屁了
So you're saying the papers are bullshit?
我只是觉得这些文件
I'm just saying they lacked some of the explosiveness
少了些应该有的爆点
it was suggested they might have.
这个嘛
Well...
我可以向公众
I can reposition the context
公开文本内容  也许
in the public arena. Maybe...
也许我能惹恼某个人
Maybe I can flip someone up the tree.
我只是觉得咱们一直在
I just feel like sometimes we're allowing the tune
按着我爸的步调行事  丽莎
to be played at my dad's tempo, Lisa
我搞不明白为什么要这样
and I'm not sure why.
大家都说  我的律师是城里最好的
I have the, quote-unquote, "best lawyer in town".
我的故事也是最好的
I have the best story.
我他妈的还有收据   -我知道你很担心
-I have fucking receipts. -I hear you're concerned.
明天对你来说很关键
You have a big day tomorrow,
懂吗  大日子的头天晚上  总要这样度过
okay?  This happens the night before.
好好休息吧   -谢谢你
-Rest up, okay? -Thank you.
我...我
Yeah. And I...
真的  你们的贡献  我全都看在眼里
Look, I really value all the work you do, honestly.
但是  能再加把劲吗
But let's try harder.
行吗  再加把劲
Yeah? Let's try harder.
谢谢
Thank you.
【肯】
有新进展吗
有就告诉我 最近挺忙的
怎么样了
如果收到 请回复一下 好吗
兄弟 最近还好吧 我就想问问
卖我那事 有新进展吗
我怀念他那双大靴子  至少能听到他来了
I miss the big boot. At least you could hear him coming.
绝对上床了
-Clearly fucking.
爸和凯莉吗  不是吧
-Dad and Kerry? Please.
给年轻女仆看表情包  这套路老得不能再老了
Showing memes to a young menial? Tale as old as time.
不可能  他不喜欢吃窝边草
No, he hates the close proximity bang.
我听说他还是很喜欢口交
He's still really into blowjobs I hear.
你就是想给他吹萧  别搞错了
You just wanna give him a blowjob, so stop projecting.
罗慕路斯    -我确实想
Hey, Romulus.
看来他现在就想来一发
Looks like he wants one now.
是是是  干得漂亮  互联网
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Well played, the Internet.
这样  小西...   -你真恶心
-Okay, Shiv... -You're disgusting.
汤姆  雨果
Tom... Hugo.
好的  你们的爸爸
Okay. So your dad
一直在拟定周末的安排
has been drawing up priorities for the weekend.
他希望每个人狠狠打击科技公司
He wants everyone hitting anti-tech positions hard.
调控加扼制
Regulate and strangulate.
这些公司越来越强势了
They're getting too powerful.
大家都看在眼里
Everybody knows it.
别让科技公司再动我们的奶酪
Stop tech eating our lunch.
安插一个新朋友当总统
Put in a new friend at the top.
选一个不会重提我们的陈年旧案的人
One who won't fire up justice about our boring old case.
没错  也许这个人还得满肚子谦卑
Yeah. And maybe eat a bellyful of humble pie
不小心得罪总统
about accidentally knocking over their President
还把他摁在地上摩擦
and smashing him on the floor?
拉倒吧  总统脑袋秀逗
It's not our fault
也不是咱们的错
the President's brain couldn't thunk good no more.
发起进攻
Go offense.
把消息放出去  就说要是老家伙跟我们不对付
Spread it round that if the Raisin goes for us
他就是在把邮轮案政治化
he's politicizing the Cruises case.
太可悲了
It's so sad.
他的司法部门心存不满
His Justice Department has a grudge.
我好像听说司法部部长
I might have heard that the deputy AG
把我的照片贴在她标靶上
has a picture of me on her dartboard which is
极其下作
disgusting.
我们...有听说过吗
Wait, have we heard that or...
已经传得满天飞了
That is the rumor that's going around.
是啊  真不知道这谣言怎么传起来的
Yeah. Funny how these rumors get started.
是啊
Yeah.
抱歉 兄弟
还在考虑 我该怎么做选择
介意我跟你坐一辆吗  爸
Hey. Mind if I jump in with you, Dad?
好啊  小宝
Okay, Pinky.
后面的空调能不能升高一度
Can we go up a degree in the back?
你没事吧
-You okay?
非要天天这么阴阳怪气的吗
-You gonna be a fucking sourpuss?
什么  我没有啊
What? No.
只是
No, I just...
上次我们好好讲话的时候
The last time that we talked properly,
你在股东大会上羞辱了我
you humiliated me at the shareholder meeting,
所以 我想我该和你谈谈
so I thought I should just check in.
那天不好过  我状态不好
It was a long day, and I was unwell.
我得说  我很关心
Well... I wanna say I'm concerned
你这周末会支持谁
about who you might endorse this weekend.
副总统   -你难道害怕戴夫·鲍耶尔
The Vice President. You're scared of Dave Boyer?
怕啊
Yeah.
看到自己有机会做老大的老二
Nothing is more dangerous than a second-rate individual
是最危险的
who sees his chance.
我必须有话语权[把勺子泡在汤里]
I need to keep my spoon in the soup.
行吧
Fine. And...
我觉得罗曼不适合当这次的发言人
I don't think this is the place to let Roman be the mouthpiece.
他长大了   -我知道  我也很爱他
-He's maturing. -Yeah, and I love him.
但他搞砸了和老家伙的通话
But he fucked up the phone call with the Raisin.
埋下了隐患
That's an existential risk.
而且他在洛杉矶做过唯一拿得出手的事情
And the only solid thing he actioned in LA, Dad
就是拍了部电影“喇叭博士?
was the movie Dr. Honk
讲了一个能和汽车对话的人
about the man who could talk to cars.
不是吗
Yeah.
但大家都带着各目的目标走进去
And we're walking in there with a different hundred aims
我觉得需要一些启发
and I think some nuance is required.
倒是还好  我们还有个公司能挡在前面
I'm just glad that we still have a company to act on behalf of.
多亏有我
Thanks to me.
凯莉  给小西搬个奖
Kerry, give Shiv a fucking medal.
好了  够了  -走吧
-All right, enough. -Let's go.
别碰我
Don't touch me.
好的  向左就是电梯
Okay, so, if you guys go to the left, the elevator is to the left.
这是你们的房门钥匙  二十分钟后开始提供迎宾酒
I have your room keys and welcome drinks start in 20 minutes.
真的能闻到恐慌的味道
Wow. I can really smell the panic.
元首地堡的气氛
Berlin Bunker vibes.
相当浓郁
It is rather pungent.
自由党的弱智女士  感觉怎么样
Well, Ms. Libtard, how you do like spelunking
在大象的屁眼里探险
in the elephant's asshole?
我只是个企业观察家  -行吧
I'm just a corporate observer.  Okay.
等这个周末结束
Well, wait till the weekend's over.
我们会让你全身都散发 白人直男癌的臭味
We'll get our white cis male stank all over you.
我太不知所措了
It's just... it's such a thrill.
我可能是俄克拉荷马州 您最铁的粉丝了
I'm the probably the biggest Conhead in Oklahoma.
想起来了“皮特小乞丐“
Of course, Panhandle Pete.
你见过马克西姆·皮尔斯了吗  我的参谋长
You've met Maxim Pierce. He's my intellectual heft.
保佑我上[环绕 DC的] 环路的菩萨
My Beltway Buddha.
我们互相督促  互相帮助  携手前行
I push him, he pushes me, and around and around we go.
难道只有我觉得 在这个人人都像蒂莫西·迈克威的房间里
Is it just me or in a room full of Timothy McVeighs
瞬间显得  康纳像罗斯福家族的人吗
does Connor suddenly look like a Roosevelt?
亲爱的
Sweetie,
这是“皮特小乞丐"啊
it's Panhandle Pete.
这位愁眉苦脸的人  本想待在家
Frowny face here wanted to stay home
写她的剧本
and work on her play
但是我需要我的长腿玛丽·托德[林肯妻子]在身达
but duty calls for my leggy Mary Todd.
没关系  我用手机就可以写剧本了
Yeah, that's fine. I can totally just write a play on my phone.
那么  你们是怎么认识的
So, how'd you two meet?
网上
-Online.
网上啊
Online.
各位好  恕我借用各位宝贵的时间
Hi, folks. Just for a second.
片刻就好
Quiet for just a second.
我要郑重感谢各位的莅临
I want to thank you all for ...
在临时通知下  拨冗出席
being here on such short notice.
也要感谢你们
And I wanna thank you
将此活动保密到位
for keeping your attendance private.
我们在本次未来自由峰会上要做的事
What we do here at the Future Freedom Summit
对于党和国家是至关重要的
is of the utmost importance to our party and our country.
我恰好又相信
I happen to believe
美利坚合众国的下一任总统
the next President of the United States
就在这间屋子里
is somewhere in this very room.
确实  而且他硬得不行了
He is, and he's hard as a rock.
希望上帝给予他力量
May God shepherd this person.
他肩负看共和党的未来
The health of our republic depends on it.
还有我的投资组合
-And the health of my portfolio.
还有那个
-And that.
敬共和党
-To the republic!
敬共和党  谢谢各位
-To the republic! Thank you.
共和党
Republic.
罗恩·佩特库斯给他儿子的射箭教练吹箫了
Ron Petkus blew his son's archery instructor.
真人真事
-True story.
吹
-Blew his arch...
刚才一个留着削边头的男的  叫我娘娘腔
Some guy with an undercut just called me Soy Boy?
别担心  格雷格
Oh, don't worry, Greg.
这儿很安全
It's a nice safe space
在这儿  你不用假装喜欢"汉密尔顿
where you don't have to pretend to like Hamilton.
可我喜欢“汉密尔顿"啊
-Well, I like Hamilton.
你当然喜欢  我们也都喜欢
-Sure, you do. We all do.
所以这... 这儿究竟是于什么的
So, what is this actually here?
就是个政治会议
This is just a nice political conference
聚集着志同道合的捐款人和知识分子们
of like-minded donors and intellectuals.
说白了  就是选择下一任总统
AKA picking the next President.
选 择 总 统
Selecto el presidento.
不是...不是这么操作的
That's not really how it works.
说不是  但就是
Yeah, no. Sure, but, yeah.
但这么做  符合宪法吗
But is that like constitutional?
我不知道  格雷格
Oh, I don't know, Greg.
你要喊一个裁判来吗
You wanna call the referee?
你见这厅里有政府巡查员吗
-Is there an ombudsman in the house?
都到齐了   -什么是政府巡查员
-Well... Here they are. What is a ombudsman
因为这家人  我们痛失总统的职位
The family who lost us a presidency.
他还好吗  老家伙
How is he, the Raisin?
再过半年  他就失业了
He's out of a job in six months.
这期间  他就是坡脚皇帝  老大党[共和党]也身处水深火热之中
Lame in the interim, and the GOP is in flames.
大家的态度都瞬息万变
We're all doing backflips.
不好意思啦
-Sorry about that.
他的健康状态十分不好
-He's got a serious condition.
我们认为大众有权利知道
We felt the country needed to know.
那你有听到什么消息吗
So, what are you hearing?
既然总统出局了  我们需要一个候选人
Well, with the president out, we need a nominee.
欢迎来到小丑城
So welcome to clown town.
还有半年就大选了  但没有候选人
Six months to Election Day, and no candidate.
超级星期二[预选阶段]已过  选票也结算了
Super Tuesday's gone, ballots are already finalized.
当然  选民代表们会在共和党全国委员会上选出候选人  但是.
The delegates will choose at the RNC, of course  but
说实在的
I think we can all be real
我们需要先在这儿选出一个人来
and say we need to choose here first.
是鲍耶尔  对吧  我们要选他吗
It's Boyer, right? We're going Boyer?
对  副总统是最保险的选择
Yup. Cleanest option is the Vice President.
我党需要团结起来
The party needs to be united.
所以我希望  你自己搞出来的烂摊子
So I hope since you started this mess
你自己收拾
you can help us clear it up.
戴夫不错  我喜欢他   -我们都喜欢
Dave's good. I like Dave. -We all like Dave.
沉稳的实干型
-Steady old plow horse.
我听说他女儿让他吃素了
I heard his daughter has made him go vegetarian.
你听说过吗   -没有
-Did you hear that? -No.
不 不 我记得我见过他吃肉丸啊
No. Oh, no, I think I've seen him eat a meatball.
不可能  站在那边的正是个隐秘的食草动物
No. Secret herbivore, Right hear.
鲍耶尔  该他了
Boyer? It's his turn?
我其实不在意他舔嘴唇的毛病
I don't really mind the lip licking thing.
不会吗
No.
很明显吗   -也还好  只是
-Is it bad? -Not really. It's just...
当你意识到他这个毛病后...就会在意
when you notice it, you definitely notice it.
只要他别在辩论大会时犯这毛病
As long as he doesn't do it much during the debates
应该就没事了
we should be fine.
那人的嘴唇绝对是北美最湿润的
The guy must have the wettest lips in North America.
是  不知道的人  还以为他是卡通里的熊
Yeah. It's like he's a cartoon bear
身旁总有个野餐篮  让他垂延欲滴
and there's always a picnic hamper nearby.
但戴夫也挺不错
Yeah, but Dave's great.
话说回来  恭喜啊
-Congratulations, by the way.
好的
-Oh, okay.
为什么  我又干了什么好事吗
For what? What have I done now?
婚礼啊
For the wedding.
你母亲的
Your mother.
卡洛琳·科林伍德 是你母亲  不是吗
Your mother is Caroline Collingwood, no?
是的..  -她要结婚了  不是吗
-Yeah. -She's getting married, no?
嫁给彼得·穆尼昂
-Peter Munion?
不可能  她正和一个叫罗里
-No, she's in a relationship with a canoe
身材像独木舟的绅士交往中
-shaped gentleman named Rory.
不是
Nope.
那可能是我记错人了.. 我没有
Maybe it was somebody else. Pretty sure... No.
好家伙
Look at that.
你懂的
You know how it is.
原生家庭啊  你可以把这个转发给我吗
Families.  Could you forward that to me, actually?
谢谢  我们回头见  谢谢啊
Thank you. I'll see you around. Thank you.
好
Okay
能麻烦你回避一下吗
Hey. Could you excuse us for just a moment?
当然当然   -感谢
-Certainly. -Thank you so much.
你已经知道了吗  你这个心机婊
Did you know about this, you withholding bitch?
什么
What?
格林  那个脱欧变态
You know Glyn the Brexit pervert?
他刚传了这个给我
Yeah, he just sent this to me.
显然  我们的母亲要嫁给一个叫彼得·穆尼昂的人
Apparently, our mother's marrying a Peter Munion.
什么“彼得·洋葱”是谁    -我他妈怎么知道
-What? Who's Peter Onion? -I don't fucking know.
不晓得那个臭屁老大知不知道
I wonder if that first born fucker knew.
打给他
Call him.
抱歉  失陪一下
Sorry. Just give me a second.
怎么了
-Yeah. What?
我和小西在一块儿  顺带通知你  新爸爸要登场了
-I'm here with Shiv. Just wanted to let you know, new dad just dropped.
不好意思  你说什么
-I'm sorry. What?
老妈要再婚了  白痴
-Yeah. Mommy's getting remarried, dingus.
你知道了吗  -他当然不知道
-Did you know?  Of course, he didn't know.
咱妈烦死肯了
Ken bores the shit out of Mom.
你们到底在说什么
What are you even talking about?
你们是指罗里吗
You mean Rory?
不是  她把罗里甩到西伯利亚了
No. She took the view "fuck Rory."
喂  小西  你们真的在“仇恨狂欢节“吗
Hey, Shiv, is it true, you're at that hate-fest fest?
在弗吉尼亚州的纽伦堡
Burning books and measuring skulls
烧毁书本  测量头骨   -是啊
down in Nuremberg, Virginia?  Yeah.
那你周末要干什么
What are you doing with your weekend?
计划着怎么将我们送进监狱吗  你最爱做的事
Planning to send us all to jail, your favorite?
行了  只是想让你知道
All right. Just wanted to let you know
老妈还是不爱你  再见  肯  挂了
Mommy still doesn't love you. Bye, Ken. Bye.
老兄  我...  我想要
Hey, man. I just wanted to
跟你谈点事儿
broach something with you.
谈吧  格雷格
Broach away, Greg.
是这样的  听着  我...我很焦虑
So, yeah. Look, I'm pretty anxious.
肯说  他可能会卖我
Ken is saying he might burn me.
你在威胁我吗
Are you threatening me?
你威胁不了我  我已经没什么好怕的了
You can't threaten me. I'm immune.
不是的  汤姆  我只是需要点建议
No, Tom. I was just thinking about advice
因为我
because I'm
我止不住地想监狱这档子事
obsessing over the prison of it all.
我只想知道  怎么才能不想了
And, I just need to know how to stop thinking.
懂   -总在我脑子里盘旋
-Yeah. -It's just constant.
我试过了  没用
I tried that. Doesn't work.
所以  我建议你   反而是一直想着这件事
You know, what I'm preferring is to always think about it.
然后  当你一度走神时  就会觉得
And then, when you don't, for a moment it's like
那只冰凉的紧擦我内脏的手放松了
"Oh, someone's loosened their icy grip on my innards."
好
Yeah.
我喜欢  我喜欢这个故事
I like that. I like it.
你想尝尝吗
So you wanna try?
这是黑皮诺
It's the Spatburgunder.
我们的葡萄园产的
Our vineyard.
是螺旋盖的
Oh, screw top.
新闻标题: 都市精英们 在拖垮我们的国家
黑色和棕色的头像来低毁
你听说鲍耶尔大势已去了吗
Did you hear Boyer's losing juice now?
民主党...   -这是生物动力法酿造的
So it's biodynamic.
味儿还挺重
Has quite a funk to it.
由民主党全国委员会及 LSM 策划
连同科技巨头金主
现在  我们其他人
你得去主动地感受  对不对
Yeah, you kind of have to meet it halfway, right? It's...
尝着有股泥土味   -是的
You know, it's...  -earthy? -Yeah.
有点... 德式的感觉  是啊
Kind of Germanic. Yeah,
风味很复杂  需要细品...  尝着不是花香味
there's lots to unpack.  It's not floral.
也不甜  而且...
It's not sugary
不是植物香气
or vegetal.
这  这
It's...
一股子村酿的感觉
It's quite agricultural, you know.
这个..这个.....
It's...It's a...
你不是个老顽固
You know you are not a bigot...
这酒不怎么样  是不是  小西
It's not very nice, is it, the wine, Shiv?
是真的  我们经常看到这种
Its true, we see it a lot
这种所谓的致歉.. 你知道吗
This so-called apology, you know
如果鲍耶尔陨落  那么也许就到了
if Boyer flames out then maybe it's time to...
到了换边站的时候了
It might be time to pivot party.
我的监狱顾问联系我
So my prison consultant called
听说北部的监狱好像满了
and it looks like the place upstate might be full.
剥夺了百人工薪阶层的权力.
Disempower the white working class
味道都一样,   -好吧 你是太累了
-It's all the same. -Well...You're tired
明早就能感觉好点了
You'll feel better about that in the morning.
是吗
Oh, yeah?
离我关禁闭的日子又近一天了  不是吗
One day closer to my incarceration, right?
好像监狱里的东西都没什么味道
Apparently, the food in jail is really bland.
我是说  我知道每天
-I know it's the same every day...
汤姆  -都一样  可是
-Tom!...but it's...
我不懂  你为什么老是想说这个
I don't get why you keep wanting to talk about it.
好吧  对不起
Okay. I'm sorry.
我总说即将到来的监狱生活  让你觉得无聊了吗
Does the topic of my imminent imprisonment bore you?
别这样  你就是...你太焦灼了  我只是.
Come on, you're just obsessing. I just...
我没法跟你一样  翻来覆去地瞎想  行吗
I can't keep going round and round, okay?
亲爱的  我不知道我还有什么可说的了
Honey, I don't know what else there is to say.
向你道歉
I'm sorry.
嘿...嘿
-Hey. -Hey.
不要吗
No?
当然  好了
Oh, sure.
好
Okay.
你知道吗
You know what?
真的没意义了
There's not really any point.
做爱没意义吗
-To making love?
对  你还在避孕呢
-Yeah. Well, if you're still on contraception
这样感觉就像  把面糊  往墙上扔一样
it's just like throwing so much cake batter at a brick wall.
我发现自己
I think what I realized is that
对当商业编剧  并没有那么感兴趣
I'm just not that interested in being a commercial playwright.
观众让你认识到这一点的
I mean, the audience helped you discover that,
是不是亲爱的
didn't they, babe?
美貌配上智慧
Well, beauty and brains.
我可能不该说这话
I probably shouldn't say that.
我会被封杀吗
Will I be cancelled?
不会  不会
No! No.
谁知道呢  是不是  夜还长着呢
Well, who knows? You know, the night is young
是啊...我...我就想知道  你是怎么做到的
Yeah. I just... I don't know how you do it.
你是怎么凭空编出故事的
How do you make up things that aren't already there?
这你就不知道了
Oh, you don't know the half of it.
我们彻夜长谈
We talk long into the night.
交流思想...聊文学国际世界宏观微观宇宙
Ideas, literary, global macro, micro, cosmo.
我们的思维碰撞出火花[彼此碰撞]
We bounce off each other.
听起来真美好
Well, that sounds delightful.
说笑  说笑呢
-No. I mean, well, yeah.
老康
-Con?
哪天周末来庞德岭吧
You should come to Pound Ridge one weekend.
你们俩都来
Both of you.
除非你们有谁太累太忙了
Unless you're tired or busy, one.
或者都是
One and all.
我们很乐意  对不对  小妞
We'd love that, wouldn't we, chicken?
我不知道你有没有被邀请呢
I don't know if you're invited.
好  我去转悠一下
Yeah. Let me circulate.
等我回来再来滋润
And I will rehydrate this gorgeous creature
这个尤物    -你要被封杀了
on my return.  -Cancelled!
你啊
You...
有趣的家伙
Fun guy.
老康  能不能别把我抛给北部的那个老色鬼
Con, maybe don't abandon me upstate with Larry Lech here.
太隔应了
Okay? It's weird.
他很有影响力
Very influential.
我们才只是秀了秀腿而已
-We're just showing a bit of leg.
对  是我的腿   -我们共同的腿
-Yeah, my leg.  The collective leg.
他是大金主
He's a huge donor.
你就没想过  我不想把身体
And maybe I don't wanna donate my body
献给政治学吗
to political science, huh?
兄弟你好
Hey, man. What's up?
对  你..你是那个魔鬼椒
Oh, okay. Yeah, It's the ghost pepper.
火辣上市的新口味  门肯
The spicy new flavor. Mencken.
你在打什么算盘  这里的大多数人.
So what's your deal? Most people here wanna
要么想睡我  要么想杀我
fuck me or kill me.
你是什么打算
How about you?
我一直很难让自己去关心政治  所以说
I always found it hard to care about politics, so...
好  听我说
Well, listen,
我有个派对小妙招
here's my party trick, all right?
说
Okay.
把你的敌人告诉我
Tell me who your enemy is
我就能告诉你  你是谁
and I'll tell you who you are.
好的
Okay.
我记下了
Put a pin in that one.
我看过你的民调  你是匹黑马
I've seen your poll numbers. You're dark horsin' it.
大家都很支持你的那些
People are buying your whole...
他们最好接受  不然我送他们去集中营
They better buy it or I'll send them to the gulag.
终于进入正题了
Oh, okay. Now we're talking.
不不不  那不是劳改营  你懂的..
I don't know. No work camps. Yeah.
会像是夏令营一样
Like summer camps.
会打人的那种夏令营  是吧
Summer camps but with beatings, right?
不不不  不会打人
No. No beatings.
感觉不错啊
Well, this is nice.
两个酷哥  享受一些低俗的乐趣
Couple of cool guys having some disgusting fun.
你们已经知道了吗
do you guys know yet
谁会接任
who takes over?
什么?  -等老蛤蟆[指总统]
-What's that? -When they send the old
进了班房以后
Battletoad off to the hoosegow?
你爸 还是 咸猪手船长
Your dad. Admiral Grope Boat.
不是  他不会
Yeah. No, he's not.
其实不会到坐牢那个地步
That's actually not happening.
可不是嘛  那就好  其实吧
Yeah, that's right. That's... no.
这是台词  坚守你们的台词  这样很好
That's the line. Stick to the line, that's good.
按我的监狱顾问史蒂芬的说法
So according to Steven my prison consultant, this is...
进去之后吃的东西就跟这一样
you know, this is kind of what the food is like inside.
我在学着适应你的蛋卷  怎么样
I'm in training. How's your omelet?
这个..
Nice.
不太..
Nope.
好吧  有点能接受了,   -这就像
Yeah. Making some inroads.
我其实很高兴你打电话给我  汤姆
I'm actually glad you called, Tom.
就像阿富汗
It's like Afghanistan.
你必须得从中间开始
You have to start in the center there.
先建立军事基地
You establish a base of operations
然后你得..向外扩展..   -好的
and you have to kind of move out -Okay.
来守住更大的领士
-to secure more territory.
我...我很怕坐牢
Yeah. I'm worried about prison.
我...我感觉自己会因为身高
I just feel because of my physical length,
会成为各种不幸事件的目标..
I could be a target for all kinds of misadventure.
里面吃的还不如这个  懂吗
And it won't taste as good as this either, okay?
你还得去掉你正在吃的这个  齁咸瑜伽垫
You have to take off 30 to 50% of the taste
百分之三十到五十的味道
of that endless salty gym mat that you're eating.
就像骆驼阴唇
The camel's labia.
好  他们会拿你的枕套擦屁股
Yeah. Like they wipe their ass on your pillowcase.
我知道  -他们就喜欢做这种事情
-I know. -That's something they like to do.
我看过监狱博客  格雷格
I've read the prison blogs, Greg.
我知道
I know.
那个
Look...
你知道..
You know how...
办公室里的人  都叫你什么吗..
they're calling you that name around the office? The...
叫圣诞树...
-You know, the Christmas tree?
直接掐灭你的希望  好在
-What's good is to eradicate hope.
如果你没有希望  就没法伤害到你
They can't get you if you got no hope.
叫你这个称号  应该是因为...
It's because I think...
那些 你想甩掉罪责
you know, if you have a crime you need to unload
他们能把它像装饰品一样 挂在你身上
they can hang it from you like an ornament.
我已经八天没睡过好觉了
I haven't really slept properly in about eight days.
这个绰号不太好
It's not a nice name,
但我在想
but... I was wondering since...
既然你无论如何都要进去了..
I mean, it looks like you're going anyway.
你...你能不能...
Is it possible you might...
帮我一把
With me?
你是想问  你能不能...
Are you asking if you can...
把你那一连串企业不法行为
hook your bauble of corporate wrongdoing
挂在我的枝丫上吗  格雷格
on one of my branches, Greg?
我只是觉得  如果..
I just thought if
如果这对你讲没什么差别的话
it won't make much difference to you...
好吧  行吧
Fine. Okay.
把我挂满吧  你个混蛋
Load me up, you piece of shit.
没有交换条件吗  就...
No quid pro quo? Just...
你...你真是太好了
That's... That's incredibly kind of you.
我来买单吧   -不用了
-Can I get this? -No.
绿色和平“窃取了你的遗产
Greenpeace stole your inheritance.
再说了  很快  我的一日三餐就都免费了  所以..
Besides, all my meals will be free soon, so...
好了  罗伊先生
Okay, Mr. Roy.
你还知道哪些
Is there any other illegal conduct
与我们今天讨论的内容有关
that you are aware of in connection
但没有被提及的
to what we've been talking about today
违法行为吗
that we haven't covered?
没有了   暂时想不到更多了
No. Not that I can think of now.
就目前而言
At the moment.
谢谢你抽出时间  罗伊先生
Thank you for your time, Mr. Roy.
律师
-Counselor. -Thank you.
谢谢
Thank you.
很好  我觉得
Good. I think that...
你表现不错
you did fine.
开局不错
It was a good start
他们会再安排一次会面
and they'll have another session.
可以说  进展很糟  丽莎  没关系
We can say it went badly, Lisa. It's okay.
好吧  我们可以... 我们..
Okay. Let's maybe just...
我们可以周一早晨再复盘一下
We'll do the Monday morning quarterback in a bit.
他们花了一整天时间  在我的陈述中
They spent all day trying to find hairline fractures
寻找破绽
in my story.
相比之下  我爸的腐败就像海啸的规模一样大
Meanwhile, my dad's a fucking tsunami of corruption.
他们不会给你友善的抱抱  肯
-They don't do cuddles, Ken.
是没有
-Right.
因为  我...我知道是为什么
Right. Because I know how this works.
对吧  我爸花了点小钱
Okay? My dad is drowning them
说了点好话  就收买了他们
in chicken feed and compliance bullshit.
接下来  我们知道的就是五年过去了
Five years go by, and it's
人们问“那啥那场..   -别说了
"Hey, whatever happened to that big investigation
对坏人的大调查  结果如何
-into the bad people?"
肯   -你知道吗
-Ken? Because you know what?
他们害怕我爸   -别这样
They're scared of my dad.  Come on.
别这样  -他们假装自己站在正义的一边
They pretend they're on the side of justice.
他们假装自己站在检举者的一边
They pretend they're on the side of the whistleblowers.
别在这里说  但他们都是胆小鬼
-Not here. -But they're chickenshit.
别在这里说
Not here.
这下  应该能给他们点压力了
That should put a rocket up their asses.
我们不希望这件事被政治化
We do not want this to get politicized.
一切都是政治
Well, everything is politics,
所以   -肯德尔
so... Kendall.
你觉得 你比我还聪明吗
Do you think you're smarter than me?
什么  我...  什么  没有
What? Do I... What? No.
没有   -也许你确实比我聪明
-No. -Because maybe you are.
但我是更专业的律师
But I am a better lawyer.
你表现得专横跋扈  戒备心强
You acted high-handed and defensive
偶尔又变得太过随便
and then oscillated to wildly over-familiar and glib.
油腔滑调  你有时会削弱我的权威
You sometimes undermined my status
对你自己的牵连程度也不够坦诚
and didn't appear to be frank about your own involvement.
我们都暂停反思一下  可以吗
But let's take stock, okay?
你好  洛根
Hey, Logan.
戴夫 你好吗   -好 好
Dave. How are we?  Good. Good.
很高兴偶遇你
I'm glad I ran into you.
我觉得我们很少有机会沟通沟通
I feel like we've hardly had a chance to connect.
现在有了   -现在有了
-Well, here we are. -Here we are.
你听说 他们称这为泛美初选了吗
You've heard they're calling this the ATN primary?
我不担心这些
Oh, I wouldn't worry about all that.
我想和你讨论的
You know, one of the things
其中一件事是
I wanted to discuss with you is...
控制科技公司
is Controlling Tech.
那是我非常非常重要的一项政纲
That's a big, big plank for me.
有意思
Oh, that's interesting.
真有意思   -确实
That's really interesting. Sure.
确实 我
And I...
我有时会担心你们这些传统媒体
I can sometimes fear a degree of legal overreach
会在一定程度上对法律过度干预
against you legacy media guys.
你听说了  司法部副部长有一个
You heard this thing that the deputy AG has a
印着我的脸的 飞镖靶吗
dartboard with my face on it?
听说了
-Yeah.
我觉得...那只是一个谣言
I mean, I think that's just a rumor.
在我看来  这种事即便不是真的
I mean, to me, it's one of those things where
也有理由让人
even if it isn't real
感觉它是真的对吧
there's a reason it feels like it is, right?
好吧
Right.
好了  很好
Okay. Good.
听着  我就直说吧
Look, I'm just gonna be straight with you.
我喜欢你
I like you.
佩特库斯和那些大富翁都在观望
Petkus and the big dollar guys are on the fence.
让我们...让我们实现这一目标吧
Let's make this happen, yeah?
行吗  我只需要你
I just need you to
助我一臂之力
push me over the brink here.
很好  我明白了
Great. I get it.
晚宴上见
See you at dinner.
我觉得他已经在那
I think he's been waiting there for me
等我十分钟了
for the last ten fucking minutes.
好吧 好吧 好吧 那么
Okay... So Comfry, Lisa's out.
康福莉丽莎出局了  事实证明她不是个善茬
It turns out she's a toxic person.
等我组建好一个新的一流法律团队
You know? And once I get the new legal A-team in place
我们就找个合适的机会公布消息
we gotta put that out with the right context,
好吗   -好
okay?  -Okay.
没什么大不了的
Yeah, it's not a big deal.
这是一个机会  只要我们
It's an opportunity. We just,
有大人物加持
you know, flip a big name.
就万事俱备了    -没错
-Boom. It's all good. -Totally.
万事俱备,   -好可以我会告诉巴里的
-It's all good. -All right. Cool. I will tell Berry.
好了  各位  我的四十大寿
Okay, guys. B-Day. Big 4-0.
情况如何   -一切顺利
-How we looking? -Shit slaps.
是吗  你这么觉得吗  我喜欢的那个主题...叫什么来着
Yeah? You think? What was the one I liked?
我喜欢的主题叫什么来着   -“终结时代
-What's the one I liked? -End Times?
是吗   -魏玛遇上迦太基
-Right. -Weimar meets Carthage
遇上但丁  遇上人工智能   -好
-meets Dante meets AI... -Right.
耐抗生素的超级病菌
...and antibiotic resistant superbugs.
有一说一  那个挺牛的
That's kind  of dope though.
恒扎迪·史密斯 作家
I mean, but are Zadie Smith
查克· D 歌手 和卢卡斯·马德森
and fucking Chuck D and Lucas Madison
不是要来参加我的抗生素派对吗
gonna come to my antibiotics party?
不知道
I don't know.
他答应见面了吗  -他不接
-Will he meet? -He's not picking up
由我们的任何号码打的电话
any of our numbers.
好吧  再用些新号   -好的
-Okay. Well, get me new numbers. -Okay.
继续打电话  继续打
Just let's keep calling. Keep calling.
以他为先  杰西   -好的
-He is priority one, Jess. -Yeah.
我外公
Well, my grandpa
把我的遗产捐给了“绿色和平
gave my inheritance to Greenpeace
然后有人在他们的网站上发布了一条
and then someone posted a comment on their website
可能包含了对我人格侮辱的评论
and it could contain a slight on my character.
然后“绿色和平"置顶了那条评论
And then Greenpeace promoted the comment
所以  我的律师认为这是诽谤
and so my lawyer thinks that that's defamation.
这就是我起诉“绿色和平"的原因
So yeah, that's how I'm trying to sue Greenpeace.
是小西·罗伊吗
-Is that Shiv Roy?
萨尔加多先生
-Oh, Mr. Salgado.
很高兴在这儿见到你
Good to see you here.
这是否意味着  你总算想通了
Does this mean you've finally come to your senses?
不是  只是过来找找灵感
Oh, no. Just shopping in the marketplace of ideas.
参与进来吧  小西  局面很好
Step on in, Shiv, the water's fine.
我不是催促你  但是...
Hey, I don't mean to bum-rush you here, but...
你能帮我解围吗
could you help me out?
大家都想拉拢你父亲  但我..
There's a feeding frenzy around your dad
我想脱颖而出  有别于那些..
and I'm trying to stand apart from the rest of it, you know.
那些失去理智的疯子吗
The total fucking wack jobs?
不要误会我  我听取民意
Don't get me wrong. I'm with the base.
现在的能量相当惊人
Energy is extraordinary.
我只是认为我可以让传统保守派
I just think I can bring traditional conservatives
进行更多样化的对话
to a more diverse dialogue.
泛美对你的曝光度不够  的确如此
ATN hasn't given you a lot of shine. It's true.
我不想失礼  但是...我觉得
Not to be indiscreet, but I just feel...
如果我入主白宫  而你进入最高管理层
if I was in the White House, and you were in the C-suite
我们可以建立影响力
we could mold.
先生  你太直接了
Oh, wow. Sir, you are very forward.
这很直接吗
Was that forward?
让你爸助我当上总统
Get your old man to make me President.
我就保证你能当上首席执行官
I'll see to it that you become CEO.
就算是得把你爸关进监狱
Even if I have to send your dad to prison.
这..太有意思了
Well, that is very funny.
说定了吗
So it's decided?
你帮我搞定  我就把你爸送进大牢
You land this for me, I send your dad up the river?
我是说除非...
Yeah. I mean, unless
除非他一个月内退休
he resigns in a month.
干净利落
Clean kill, baby!
真不错
Good stuff. Okay.
很好笑
Very funny.
你们不是想听建议吗
Look, you want some advice?
囤积鲭鱼罐头
Hoard mackerel tins.
听起来很滑稽吧
I know. Sounds funny, right?
但可以用来以物换物
But you're gonna need them for bartering.
是吗    -没错
-Yeah. -Yeah.
格雷格  你能记下来吗
Greg, can you... will you keep a note?
好的   -还有马桶
-Oh, yeah. -Oh, and the toilet.
马桶可以是你的爬楼机
Your toilet is your stair machine,
你的凳子冰箱
it's your bench it's your fridge,
是你的...爱人
it's your lover
还可以是兄弟  牧师啊
it's your brother, it's your priest.
当然  最重要的它还是你的..马桶
Oh, and also, most importantly it's also your toilet.
好   -没错
Right.
我是说...那是..
Yeah. That... I mean,
是监狱重要的一部分
that's a big part of prison.
它能温文尔雅
It can be a perfect gentleman.
也能十分操蛋
It could also be a terrible bastard.
马桶会很操蛋吗
Your toilet could be a bastard?
团结才是关键
The key is unity.
要是我们能夺人所爱  我就投入巨额资金
If we land a favorite, I can pool the big money.
但我得知道  舆论是站在我这边的
But I need to know the messaging will be there to back me up.
我很喜欢他  但很多人都心存疑虑
I like him, but a lot of people are asking,
鲍耶尔是不是斗士
"Is Boyer a fighter?"
我不在乎他的履历
I don't care about the resume
也不在乎意识形态的纯粹性  只要他们能成功
or ideological purity  as long as they get it
能成仁
and they pop.
你要是想找这样的人
You're looking for someone who gets it,
我刚好有人选
I got your man.
康纳·罗伊  有品牌
Connor Roy. He's got a brand name,
有竞选资金  民粹主义吸引力
a war chest  populist appeal.
他更是名斗士   -谢了 皮特
And he's a fighter.  Hey, thanks, Pete.
我相信 能替我父亲
I believe I speak for my father
坚定不移地讲出
when I offer a firm and robust
不予评论
"No comment."
的确如此
Sure.
我能预见康纳上位的样子   -当然  我赞成
-I could see Connor. -Sure, I agree.
看来你已拔出石中剑了  我的国王
The sword has been pulled from the stone, my liege.
看看我们谈笑风生
Look at us playing nice,
大家会觉得我们情投意合
people might think we liked each other.
不不不  我是保守党
No, what? Hey, I'm a conservative.
我热爱传统
I like tradition.
我为鲍耶尔副总统年复一年的效劳致敬
I doff my cap to Vice President Boyer's years of loyal service.
谢谢
Thank you.
我记得你以前叫我“马丁·范无趣
I believe you used to call me "Martin Van Boring"?
别啊  记什么仇呢  我现在还这么叫你
Hey, come on, no. I still call you that.
我和门肯 虽然在某些方面有分歧  但是
Mencken and I may differ in some areas but we
我们都同意这个政党
both agree that this is the party
是属于工薪阶级的
of the working class now.
怎么了  小西
What, Shiv?
全美最富有的州都是蓝派
All the richest counties in America are blue.
民主党和科技巨头牵断了所有财富
The Democrats and Tech hold all the wealth.
我只是觉得有些咱们的人在自由派[左翼] 待久了
I just think some of us get so high off owning the libs,
都忘了谈政策
we forget to talk policy.
是啊  瑞克最爱谈政策了
Yeah, Rick loves to talk policy.
因为他把2012年刊的"国家评论"
What he does is he memorizes a National Review
背得滚瓜烂熟
issue from 2012
然后再复述给大家
and then he recites it back to you.
这政策不错   -杰瑞德讨厌谈政策
Cool policy, bro.  -And Jeryd hates to talk policy
因为要谈的话  你得先有才行
because it would mean, you know having one.
扎心窝了 兄弟
Sick burn, brosef.
没有 没有  就是开开玩笑
No. We're kidding.
我们都喜欢对方  我还会听他的演讲
We like each other.  I listen to his speeches every night.
每晚都听助眠神器
They help me drop off.
为新阶级想出民粹主义解决方案
Maybe it's boring talking about populist solutions
对你可能太无聊了  -瑞克 拜托
for working families.  Rick, come on,
你对着里根的大头贴  打了三十年飞机
you jerked off to Reagan's headshot for 30 years
现在居然开始代言劳苦大众了
and now you're Tom Joad?
天啊  太尼玛无聊了
Oh, God, it's so fucking boring.
什么意思
What's that?
你说什么
What?
我只是...看惯了你的招数
No, I just... I've seen your thing quite a lot.
什么...我有什么招数
And that, what's that? What's my thing?
油管上挑起对立的烂片
YouTube provocateur bullshit
贵族民粹主义
Aristo-populism,
强暴是天性  遵从内心的选择吧  宝贝
rape is natural.  "It's all red pill, baby."
我真他妈是有点受不了了
I'm just... I'm just so fucking over it.
你读过柏拉图吗
Have you read Plato?
当然
Yeah.
说说吧 柏拉图讲什么了
Remind me, what happens?
看看柏拉图  看看柏拉图
Read Plato!  Read Plato!
我不想看  我他妈才不要看
Oh, don't want to! Don't fucking want to!
看吧  他根本不想讨论
See, he doesn't actually wanna have a conversation.
对   -他就是想大吵大闹
He just wants to yell loud enough
登上泛美网科
-to get on ATN.
去他妈的泛美
-Nah. fuck ATN.
说真的  虽然泛美被视作堡垒  其实已经一潭死水
No, really. ATN is treated as a bulwark but it's dead.
就像是
It's basically
养老院下午五点的布丁杯
a pudding cup at 5.00pm in the nursing home.
老实说  对我没用
Honestly, doesn't speak to me.
对我认识的人也没用
Doesn't speak to the people that I talk to.
他们把现状讲成睡前故事  纯粹为了做大股东利益
It is status quo bedtime stories to maximize shareholder value.
恐我直言  洛根·罗伊
No disrespect, Logan Roy...
曾经是个人物  但是大家清楚..
was an icon. But, you know...
他已经不再重要了
he's no longer relevant.
你认识这个屌人吗   -不认识
-You recognize this fucker? -Nope.
肌肌歪歪的疲软混蛋
fucking jelly-bone-bow-tea "pip, pip, cheerio" fucker.
你跟爸说了吗
You told Dad yet?
没有  我们得阻止婚礼进行  对吧
No. We have to stop the wedding now, right?
什么  别再对妈的新丈夫念念不忘了
What? Stop obsessing over Mom's new husband.
放下吧  谁在乎啊   -放下吧
Just get over it. Who cares? Get over it?
事情就这样发生了
It just fucking happened.
我妈要嫁给一个
Our mother is marrying some dickhead
稀牙巴的臭农民
crooked-tooth turnip man.
你这么无所谓 才有问题  好吧
What's wrong is how little you care about it
冷血婊,   -可怜的罗曼
-you frozen bitch. -Poor Rome.
幻想和妈妈上床的美梦
His dreams of porking Mom
从他润滑过的指间滑走了
slipping through his little lubed up fingers.
来了  进来
Hey. So, come in. Come in.
好   -来坐
-Yeah. -Sit.
格雷格有必要来吗
Is Greg necessary?
嘴上有个把门的
Just keep your trap shut.
乖乖看着   -好的 谢谢你 先生
Watch. All right. Thank you, sir.
格雷格视窗已经最小化
Minimizing the Greg window.
今晚有许多插科打诨的把戏
There's a lot of chaff flying by.
各显身手
A lot of flapping.
我和罗恩要约见  然后讨论出
But Ron and me are gonna meet and figure out how we can
一个共同的人选
pull for the same name.
我们只能有一种声音  否则将会分崩离析
We need one voice on this, or we could fall apart
拱手让给那些蠢驴们[指民主党]
and hand it to the fuck-fuck donkey gang.
没错
Right.
所以...
So...
我们选谁
Who do we like?
我们不该传个球吧
Well, shouldn't we kick it around a bit?
就是要想胜券在握
You know, it feels like it's poised
只要你和佩特库斯达成共识
so if you and Petkus come together
其他赞助就会跟随  然后
and then the other donors follow, then it's...
没错
Exactly.
我们来选
We're picking.
别浪费大家的时间
We haven't got all night.
我选康纳·罗伊
I like Connor Roy.
老实说  老爸  你应该支持民主党
Honestly, Dad, I think you go Dems.
我真这么想
Yeah, I do.
老天啊
Jesus Christ.
我挺喜欢门肯的  但
I kinda like Mencken, but...
但我知道  他挺烂的  所以现在鲍耶尔比较合适
I know he's kind of shitty, so if it's now, I guess, Boyer.
但我能直说吗  我不喜欢鲍耶尔
But can I just say, I don't like Boyer.
怎么  你他妈什么...   -罗曼
What? What's with the...
无意冒犯  但鲍耶尔已经是老黄历了
Roman, no disrespect, but Boyer's yesterday's papers.
民主党会以“变革"为题轻易赢过他
The Dems will run on change, and blow him away.
政治小姐
Mrs. Politics?
你作为顾问  赢过几次大选啊
How many big races did you win as a consultant?
四届  三届  你赢过两届吗   -罗曼鲍耶尔没可能赢
-Four, three? Two? Did you win two? -Roman, Boyer is not a winner
我们都心知肚明   -还是一届呢
-and we know that. -One?
那好  我们该不该和门肯聊聊
Okay. Well, then should we talk to Mencken,
看能不能达成共识   -民众中意他
see if we can deal?  The base does like him?
对吗
Right?
我能...发表意见吗  不对
Look, can I say something? No.
门肯就是个傻逼  推崇整体论和本土主义  他思想有毒
Mencken is an integralist, nativist fuckhead.  He's toxic.
他支持“全民医保禁止随胎
He's "Medicare for all, abortions for none."
还有 他的外交理念
And his idea of diplomacy
就是和维克托·欧尔班「凶牙利总理]一起打野狗子
is shooting roe deer with Viktor Orban
还有和中国打贸易战
and then starting a trade war with China.
我很强硬  我知道  会有人哗众取宠
Look, I'm tough. I know that there's the carnival bark
还有一堆傻逼做戏  但是
and then there's the fucking show but
他不属于美国政治传统
he is outside the American political tradition.
我认为 作为韦斯达 我们有责任..
And I think we have a responsibility as Waystar
对于...对于美利坚合众国还有
to the American Republic
对未来的..
and to the future of...
操你妈 罗曼   -八十 不知道多少年前..
-fuck you, Roman. -Four score years and whatever.
他还谈到了...   -我的妹妹
-No, he has talked about... -My sister did bring forth
从她的卧室里带出了一杯浓痰「改编自葛底斯堡演说]
from her bedroom a cup of milky sputum.
你说完了吗   -说完了
-You done? -Yeah, done.
门肯还想焚烧古兰经
He's talked about burning Qurans
以及授权记者证   -对
-and licensing press credentials. -Yeah, I know.
他在移动奥沃顿窗口
He's just shifting the Overton window.
你居然知道这个词的意思
I'm surprised you even what that fucking is.
我当然知道   -他在打开窗口
-I do.  He's opening it
把工会组织者踢出局
and throwing union organizers out of it.
我的天啊  少恐吓我们了
Stop Chicken Little-ing us.
我们听了只想打个盹
It just makes us wanna all have a nap.
你也别像个龌龊的小妖精
Stop being a dirty little pixie
只会在老爸耳边念叻仇恨言论
whispering swastikas in Dad's ear.
你又来了  你他妈只会这招
Boom. There you go again. So fucking route one.
我没有说美国会变成纳粹德国
I'm not saying it's going to be full Third Reich.
但我是真的很担心
But I am genuinely concerned
我们可能会逐渐衰落到
that we could slide into
俄意巴[俄国 意大利 巴西]大乱炖
a Russian-Berlusconied-Brazilian fuck pile.
你有个小娇夫  几件貂毛大衣
You have a trophy husband and several fur coats.
我觉得你会没事的   -汤姆
-I think you're gonna be fine. -Tom?
你喜欢谁
-Who do you like?
我吗  我...我觉得小西说的...
-Me, I...I think Shiv
小西说得很有道理
talks a lot of sense.
但我也赞同萨尔加多
-But I also jibe with Salgado.
你"赞同”他
-Oh, you jibe with him?
汤姆 你这肯定是种族歧视   -我
-Pretty sure that's racist, Tom. -May I...
抱歉 我可以投票吗   -当然可以 兄弟
sorry, do I get to vote?    Sure you do, buddy.
你可以在选举日和其他民众一起投票
You get to vote at the election with all the other folks.
好吧
-Right, yeah.
我只是感觉在这里投票
Well, I guess, I just feel like you maybe get a bigger vote
效用大一些  -别急 卡斯特罗[古巴共和国主要缔造者]
in here  -Easy, Castro.
司法部方面  鲍耶尔可能足够变通
Boyer is likely to be flexible over the DOJ.
前提是  他得能赢  但他赢不了
Not if he doesn't win, which he won't.
但是 我们听到了风声  据说调查力度在降低
Although, we are hearing murmurs that the case is weakening
并且  不会有哪位高层
and that no one big is likely
要去服刑   -太好了
-to do jail time. -Great.
当然  除了汤姆以外
With the notable exception of Tom, obviously.
对不起 汤姆   -没事 雨果 我理解的
-Sorry, Tom. -No, please, Hugo. Understood.
爸  如果你不变蓝[支持民主党]  那么至少我们得..
Look, if you don't go blue, Dad  then at least we have to
支持萨尔加多
be backing Salgado.
疲软先生
Señor Dickless.
坦帕湾缩头乌龟长官
Captain of the Tampa Bay Cuckaneers.
抱歉 希德的电话
Cyd. Sorry. Duty calls.
工作的事情,   -我不喜欢他
Look, I don't like him,
他是新保守主义分子  却装作不是
he's a Neocon pretending to be a Paleocon
但他至少还在乎民众   -喂
-but he at least talks base and... -Hello?
汤姆
Tom.
你现在在哪
Where are you right now?
弗吉尼亚
Virginia.
我是说  你在楼里的哪个房间
No, where are you in the building?
小西  我想说
Shiv, can I just say,
我知道我们意见相左
and I know that we have had our differences
但我真心觉得  你选择褐色人种太勇敢了
but I do think you are so brave for picking the brown man.
我觉得该给你分个奖牌
I think that we should get you a medal.
天啊 特别的奖牌  颁给喜欢褐色人种的
-Amazing. Just a racist. -A special medal for white women
白人女性   -你就当个种族歧视者吧
-who like brown man. -Just being a racist now.
我是个好女孩  装作在乎民众
I'm a good girl. I pretend to care about people
因为没人在乎我
'cause no one cares about me!
对了 你有什么想跟老爸说的吗
Oh, yeah. Actually, do you have something you wanna tell Dad
关于老妈的一条消息  罗曼  你要不分享一下
from Mom, a message that maybe you could share, Rome?
是的  去你的  确实有
Yeah, wow. fuck you. Thanks. I do.
我有个消息
I have a message. Yeah.
老妈要再婚了
Mom's getting remarried.
跟柏蒂·巫夫特吗
To Bertie Woofter?
不是  跟彼得彼..穆尼昂
No, to Peter... Peter Munion.
彼得·穆尼昂   -他妈的开什么玩笑
You're fucking kidding.
那个爱闻椅子的变态吗
The seat sniffer?
他都无所事事..
He's been hanging
快四十年了   -是的  她很..
round for 40 years.  Yeah and, she would...
他们很希望
They would love it, apparently
你去参加他们盛大的托斯卡纳式婚礼
if you came to their big Tuscan wedding.
他们派你来当小信差的吗
And they sent you as messenger boy?
兄弟 嘿
-Hey, man. -Hey.
谢谢你来
-Thanks for coming.
我要特色英雄套餐  谢谢
So I will take the... Griddle Hero special, please
配双层薯饼  所有馅料都加
with double hash browns, fully loaded.
一个原味华夫饼
And a plain waffle
以及... 一大杯温水
and a large cup of room temperature water.
谢谢
Thank you.
我就看着他吃吧
I might just watch him.
你知道吗  拉斯普京[沙皇俄国妖僧] 每天吃早餐的时候
You know that Rasputin would take a dose of arsenic
会服用一剂砒霜来建立他的耐受性
with breakfast each morning to build up his tolerance.
听我说  所以..
Look, so...
我觉得你知道的...汤姆  我一直很喜欢你
I think you know, I've always liked you, Tom.
肯德尔  我也喜欢你  我是说  我有表现出来的
I like you too, Kendall. I mean, I have notes.
不  我也是
Oh, no. I have notes.
我觉得  我表现得更明显..
I think mine might be more extensive than yours.
是吗
I dont know
听我说  我可以让你摆脱困境
But, look, I think I can get you out of this mess
免除牢狱之灾
where you're going.
其实.. 都还没定数呢  所以.
Well...nothing is certain, so...
你知道他们叫你
You know they're calling you
圣诞树吗
the Christmas tree?
你知道吗
Yeah.
也许是因为我长得很高  让人愉悦
Perhaps that's because I'm tall and jolly.
可能吧  你是这样想的吗
Maybe. You think?
但我觉得  你其实不想被当做
But I think maybe you don't wanna be the chit
公司走投无路时 献出的祭品
the company offers up when it has no choice.
这
Well...
当然  我希望不会发生那样的事
obviously, I'd prefer that not to happen.
但是..
But...
这很复杂   -是的
-it's complicated. -It is.
但我来是想问你  你对别的选择感兴趣吗
But I'm here to ask, are you interested
理论上来说
in an alternative, theoretically
最近
I have of late
我决心 不再怀揣希望地等了
decided not to tarry too much with hope.
好吧  我的案子...
Okay. Well, my case is...
我的案子很猛  它...不是...它...
It's strong. No, it's...
我的案子还可以
My case is fine.
它有缺陷
It has gaps.
但如果我这边有人可以站出来说
But if I had someone who could say that
所有文件都要经过我爸的批准
nothing gets signed off on without my dad's say so
我们都知道  这就是事实
which, I think, we both know to be true.
我...   -那么...
Ooh, I don't know that
肯  这我就不知道了
I do know that, Ken.
我只是名谦卑的仆人  肯
Yeah, I'm just a humble servant, Ken.
兄弟  我尊敬你
I admire you, man.
我真的太他妈...敬佩你
I do. I fucking... you know, you're...
你..看看..你千里迢迢
Look, you're a long way from home.
远走他乡
You're far from the tree.
你打了一手好牌
You've played your hand well,
坐在最有权势的主桌
and you're sitting at the top table.
哪里哪里  谢谢你
Well, shucks. Thank you.
我只是爱上了你妹妹  仅此而已
I fell in love with your sister, that's what happened.
当然  对 对
Sure. Oh, yeah. Right...
的确兄弟
sure, man.
乡村老鼠和极品辣妹  改编自伊索寓言
The country mouse and the hot tamale.
那你只是
And you're just...
什么...
What? Just...
我想你只是 一大杯水
I suppose you're just a long glass of water?
没别的意图   -我想是吧
-No agenda? -I guess.
情况是这样的
Well, here's how it goes.
我请了巨他妈牛逼的新律师
I have new lawyers who are fucking amazing.
我不会低估
I do not underestimate
你正在经历的内心冲突
the cognitive dissonance you're experiencing.
撒谎 躲藏
Lying, hiding.
但很快  就能获得免予公诉
But pretty soon granted immunity.
你就不用去坐牢了
And you're not going to prison.
听上去如何
How does that sound?
我想还有其他人选
I guess there are other names.
在此事上  我们得团结一致
We have to be united on this.
如果我们分裂了 那就是一场灾难
It's a disaster if we splinter.
萨尔加多的言论很棒
Salgado has great narrative.
别拍萨尔加多的马屁了  小西
Quit butt-huffing Salgado, Shiv.
你要是在路边摆个柠檬水摊  我们都支持
We all supported your little DC lemonade stand
但这是现实世界  这才是大事
but this is the fucking real world. This actually matters.
罗曼  你喜欢那只靴子
Roman, you just love the boot
是因为喜欢有人穿它来踢你
because you love to be kicked by it.
怎么了
What?
什么
不  没什么
Nothing. No.
康纳如何
What about Connor?
有意思
Interesting.
我相信这个想法有很好的前景
I do believe that idea has good promise.
真的
I do.
可以想象
I could see it.
你要是能想象  我们要不讨论一下
Well, if you can see it, should we talk about it?
孩子们   -可以  我不知道
Kids?  Sure. I don't know.
好吧
Yeah.
但是...真的吗
Wait, but like really?
应该吧
I guess.
可以吧  我不知道
Sure.  I don't know.
反正他们都是群怪胎  有啥不行呢
They're all fucking weirdos anyway so why not?
无意冒犯  老康   -我不介意
No offense, Con.  -None taken.
他人长得师
-I mean, he's a good looking kid.
在他的领域...也够聪明
He's smart, in his way.
乔·肯尼迪 老无赖 也支持过自己儿子
fucking Joe Kennedy did it for his boys.
所以 我们就让他
So let's get him in there
面带微笑擦亮皮鞋地 去参选吧
with a smile and a shoeshine
让罗恩和所有人都支持他
and get Ron and everyone behind him.
我会为这个家鞠躬尽瘁的  老爸
I would fight so fucking hard for this family, Pop.
西沃恩
Siobhan.
作为政治顾问  你有什么看法
As a political consultant, what do you think?
-说吧   -好吧 他的名头不够响亮
-Come on. -Well, okay. Not huge name ID
但姓氏会是一种助力...
but the family name will be a factor.
还有呢...  -众多正面助力之一
-And... -A positive. One of many.
他没有从政经历
He's got no track record.
一张白纸  让人无从下手
Nothing to beat me with.
毫无污点
I'm a clean skin.
还有我觉得
And I guess,
在演讲和人际关系技巧方面...   -全都满分
in terms of presentation and connection skills...  Tick, tick.
基本技能他都会[在走路时嚼口香糖]
He can walk and chew gum.
他尿得很准
He pisses pretty straight.
非常准  我是精准的政策镭射机
Pretty damn straight. I piss policy laser.
好吧  我们是认真的吗
Okay. Are we being serious about this?
我们是在说  要让康纳当选
We're talking about trying to make Connor
美国总统吓得我拉裤兜
President of the United States of America, Crap Pants.
罗曼  这里包容一切[大帐篷]  你何不一起加入
Roman, it's a big tent. Why don't you just come in?
好啊  我可能会联系给我蛋蛋脱毛的人
Sure. I might call the guy who waxes my balls.
他也有机会   -天啊
-He's a possible. -Jesus.
格雷格
Greg.
你会给康纳投票吗
Would you vote for Connor?
我吗  我会不会... 老实说...
Me? Would I...-Honestly?
老实说  我.
-Honestly, yeah? I...
看情况吧  我觉得..
It depends, I think.
我能想象自己昧心为他投上一票
I think I could see myself spoiling my ballot in his favor.
取决于对手是谁
Depending on the opposition. Yeah.
你怎么认为  小西
What do you think, Shiv?
这么做很疯狂吗
Is it nuts?
我喜欢老康  真的  但是.
I love Con, I do. But
要是认真的话  我觉得我们得..
if we're talking about this seriously, I think we have to...
考虑一下萨尔加多
look at Salgado.
我能把他带上来吗   -算了吧
-Can I bring him up here? -Oh, come on.
雨果  打给鲍耶尔
Hugo, call Boyer.
好吧  要是她把闷逼萨尔加多带上来
Okay. If she's bringing up Soggy Salgado
那我想看看我们能否驯服门肯  好吗
then I wanna see if we can tame Mencken. Okay?
真他妈服了
Oh, for fuck's sake.
开免提
Speakerphone.
喂
Hello?
你好 戴夫
Hi. Dave,
我是洛根
it's Logan.
你好吗
How are you?
很好  洛根  你怎么样
Good, Logan. How are you?
我很好  我们都很好
Oh, I'm fine. We're all fine.
我现在在套房里
I'm here in my suite.
你想顺道过来坐坐吗
Would you fancy stopping by?
很晚了  洛根
It's pretty late, Logan.
不过...好吧
But sure. Sure.
太棒了  戴夫  听我说.
Great, great. And, Dave, listen...
我的冰箱空了
my fridge is bare.
你能帮我带罐可乐上来吗
I don't suppose you could run me over a Coke?
你是说 叫客房服务吗
Did you mean to call room service?
你要是没有可乐
If you don't have a Coke
有别的什么吗
is there something else?
什么
Yes.
你能开除司法部副部长吗
Could you fire the Deputy Attorney General?
开除司法部副部长
Fire the Deputy Attorney General?
我说笑的  过来吧
I'm kidding. Come on over.
我们聊一聊
Have a chat.
要是你方便的话
If it's convenient.
好的  我一会儿就到
Sure, I'll be over in a few minutes.
谢谢  雨果
Thank you, Hugo.
带那个孩子走吧   -好的
Take the boy and go. Yeah.
我...我会走的  我只是想说  我想...
I will go. I just wanna say, I think...
我...为了我的国家  我得说
I think I owe it to my country to say.
我觉得你不该让康纳坐上皇...当总统
I don't think you should crown or make Connor president.
就这样  谢谢  晚安 抱歉
That's it. Thank you. Goodnight. Sorry.
你觉得如何
So what do you think?
-让我考虑一下   -好的 你慢慢考虑
-Let me think. -Yeah. Take your time.
我知道  这对你来说不容易 是啊
-I see. It's tough for you. -Yeah.
我爸爸看起来很强势
You know, my dad seems powerful.
小西让你很有安全感
Shiv seems safe,
但是..
but...
我不知道  你觉得她还会等在那吗
I don't know. You think she'll still be there
等你出狱
waiting for you after prison?
到底会怎样  要是我
How exactly does it work if I do come over to you?
要是我加入你的阵营
我是说...怎么可能更好
I mean, how is it better
让我告诉我妻子..
for me when I tell my wife
我爱的人
whom I love
还有这个家  说我背叛了他们
and this family, that I'm turning against them?
怎么可能
How?
她会尊重你
She'll respect you.
质问她到底在干什么  把她拉拢过来
Tell her, "What's she doing?" Bring her over.
让洛根退位
Logan goes down.
小西会知道  谁才是真男人
Shiv knows who the fucking man is.
来吧 老弟
Come on, man.
但是...我不是有意侮辱你  但是
But have... and I don't mean to be insulting, but...
相处了一阵子
having been around a bit...
我预感
my hunch...
你会完蛋的
is that you're going to get fucked.
因为我见你搞砸过很多次
Because I've seen you get fucked a lot
而我从没见洛根搞砸过一次
and I've never seen Logan get fucked once.
真好  真有风度
Nice. Classy.
行
Yeah.
好  我得走了
Okay, I gotta go.
你知道他们 在楼上套房 做什么吗
Do you know what they're doing up in his suite?
他们在选下一届总统
They're picking the next president.
格雷格  格雷格
-Greg! -Greg!
"绿色和平"去死
fuck Greenpeace!
格雷格  格雷格
-Greg! -Greg!
不...
No
格雷格 格雷格   -我没事
-Greg! -Greg! .... -I am all right
好了
Okay
很显然  我们很注重
Obviously, we take the integrity
司法部的完整性
of the Justice Department very seriously
但  总是有僭越的问题
but there is always the question of overreach.
所以  是的  针对科技公司的策略很明确
So, yeah, on tech, I mean, the strategy is clear.
我听到你说的有关 Gojo 公司的想法了
I hear you about GoJo.
我个人认为 不会有
I personally don't think there would be
任何监管方面的问题
any regulatory issues.
好吧
Well...
谢谢你 戴夫
thank you, Dave.
谢谢你 副总统先生
Thank you, Mr. Vice President.
你给了我们许多想法
You've given us a lot to think about.
很高兴再见到你   -我也是
-Great to see you again. -You, too.
真高兴再见到你  我的好对手
Wonderful to see you again, my very good adversary.
就是想稍微聊两句
So, just wanted to chitchat a little bit.
刚才很有意思
That was funny earlier, you know?
你在老爸的雷区上蹦迪
You tripping the light fantastic on grandpappy's nut sack.
我叫你爸狗屁的时候  起作用了吗
And when I called your dad bullshit? I mean, did that bump?
当然  还用说  以前从来没听过这种话
Oh, yeah, yeah. Never heard that before.
那场景简直是硬核加炮弹
Like, that was hardcore and junk.
情况是这样的  这只猴子不会跳舞[我不耍花招]
'Cause the thing is, this monkey don't dance.
你这只猴子吗   -对
-This monkey right here? -Yeah.
这只 等在爸的卫生间里的 跳舞猴子 不会跳舞吗
This dancing monkey in Dad's bathroom doesn't dance?
是的
That's right.
所以.
So
我确实想跟你聊些事
I did wanna talk to you about something.
管他的  我直接说吧
And fuck it, I'll just come out and say it.
法西斯主义有点酷
Fascists are kind of cool.
但也不太酷  所以  这对你来说问题大吗
But not really, so is that like a problem, a thing?
真的吗  问我的想法的话
Seriously? Me? I just...
我没什么界限
I don't have a lot of boundaries.
奥古斯丁[古罗马思想家] 托马斯·阿奎纳[意大利神学家]
St. Augustine, Thomas Aquinas
舒马赫[经济学家] 我乐意引用任何人的话语
Schumacher, I'll borrow from anyone.
你知道
And, you know,
如果 特拉维斯·比克尔 [电影 出租车司机 主角] 的论点好
if Franco or H or Travis Bickle had a good pitch fuck it,
我也引用  因为我通吃
I'm a Man for All Seasons.
有个非常淘气的小男孩也叫 H [希特勒]
"H"? You know, there was a very naughty boy named H...
我是个羽翼丰满的民主党人士
I'm a fully-fledged, small D democrat.
一场规范的选举
A well-regulated election
是上帝恩典的一个信号
is a transmission frequency for God's grace.
见鬼了  你真的是基督教徒
Holy shit. You really are a Christian, aren't you?
不是的  不是  我唯一关心的是  谁是利益方
Well, no... My only thing is like who's the stakeholder, right?
我已经悉心呵护
I've been tending, you know, my little garden
我的小花园  快一百年了  然后
for like a hundred years, and then...
四十个陌生人从一辆卡车后面下来
40 new guys show up in the back of a truck
扛着手提式大型录音机
playing their boom box
举行了场投票
and it's put to a vote,
随后他们决定把我的农场给他们
and they decide to give my farm to them. I mean...
我就..“打扰一下刚才发生了什么"
I'm like, "What... So sorry, what happened?"
也许你应该在收获前
Maybe you have to put in, right,
先播种  对吧   -是的
before you get to take out? Yeah.
好吧 你知道的...谁能
Okay. Well then, you know who gets to...
谁能加入呢
who gets to join?
这个嘛.. 人们相信跟自己相像的人
Well...people trust people who look like them.
这是有科学依据的
That's just a scientific fact.
他们会提供更多税款来帮助他们
They will give more tax dollars to help them.
现在
Now,
你可以加入新元素  随你便  但拜托  兄弟
you can integrate new elements, of course but come on, man,
慢点来
slowly.
恕我直言  操
I mean, fuck!
我喜欢这个国家
-I like this country.
当然   -我们暂缓一下
-Yeah.  Let's just take a beat
再来从本质上改变它的构成
before we fundamentally alter its composition.
好
Yeah.
就一件事而言
And in terms of, you know
这个...这里是有问题的  对吧
this here... there's a thing here, right?
我理解你  你是...
And I get it,
你是6G 我们是盒式录像机
you're fucking 6G, and we're Betamax.
但你知道的  你需要我们  大概吧
But, you know, you need us, I think.
我们的新闻  我们的观众  那些老不死的
Our news, our viewers. Those fucking almost-deads.
这可是块很大的蛋糕
That's a big slice of pie.
如果提名了我
Well, if I'm the nominee
他们真的会有人投反对票吗
are any of them really gonna vote against me?
不会  但是
No, but...
到了大会开始那天  一定会是一场
you know, it's going to be a fucking shit show
精彩的"大戏"
going into the convention.
我觉得你真的需要我们推你一把
I think you could really use our push.
我觉得你们也需要我
I think you could use mine.
也许吧
Maybe.
你在这场戏里的角色是什么
Where are you in all this?
我  罗曼吗
Me, Roman?
你知道的
You know...
我在爬升   -是吗
-I'm creeping on the come-up. -Oh, yeah?
是的  我对泛美的未来有些想法
Yeah. I've got some ideas for ATN, you know?
冲掉米粥 [取消乏味的节目] 加点辣椒酱[料]
Sluice out the fucking porridge and add some sriracha.
挖些抖音上的疯子过来  懂吗
Poach some of those TikTok psychos, you know?
玩枪 抽电子烟的 擦边女 之类的
E-girls with fucking guns and JUUL pods.
直接聚焦黑人和拉丁群体
You know, give me some straight shot blacks and Latinos.
不再总是这些
No more of this
枕头和便盆[让人昏昏欲睡的屎尿屁]
fucking pillows and bedpans.
我们应该只有骨头汤[或是精液]和伟哥
You know, we're strictly bone broth and dick pills.
要有深层国家阴谋论时段
Deep state conspiracy hour
但最后 又会对你使个眼色 原来也有搞怪
but with like a fucking wink, you know, funny.
还要有一部剧...
And the whole show
专为一位新星打造
is kinda set up for the star
杰瑞德·门肯总统
President Jeryd Mencken.
有人吗
Knock-knock.
听说你想要这个
Heard you wanted one.
谢谢
Thank you.
用可乐洗礼
Anointed with a Coke.
挺好的
That was nice.
他挺好的   -他..哪里好了
-He's nice. -He's not nice.
哪里好了   -爸
-He's not. -Dad...
我知道咱们是来这个市场给你买奶牛的
I know we came to market to buy you a nice milk cow
但我们给咱 淘到了一只霸王龙
but we found ourselves a fucking T-Rex, okay?
他是票房黑马  这家伙真的牛
He's box office. The guy is fucking diesel.
他很上镜  又风趣  还有力
He's good on camera. He's fun. He'll fight.
民众会府首帖耳
Viewers will eat from his hand.
无解可击   -可不是
No downside. Oh, yeah.
那咱们进军波兰吧  爸  还无解可击呢
Let's just invade Poland, Dad. No downside.
他的幕億长在集会上打破了一个孩子的下巴
-Oh, Jesus. -No, his chief of staff broke a kid's jaw at a rally.
啥情况
What
如果我们调解不了
If we don't come to an accommodation
就会被抢占先机  然后失去泛美的印钞机
we get outflanked, and we lose the ATN dollar machine
就没法跟科技公司斗了  对吧  还要收购 Gojo 呢
when we need cash to fight tech, right? And buy GoJo.
小西想让你听她的  我想让你听我的
Shiv wants her way, I want my way
康纳想让你听他的  我们打成平手
Connor wants his way, so that's even.
打什么平手啊  我的观点更重要
It's not even! My opinion counts for more.
真的  事实如此
No, it does.
好吗  我知道  真的
It just fucking does, okay? I know this. I know.
人们恨他  他们恨死这家伙了
People hate him. They fucking hate this guy.
你们必须看看與论风向
You have to look at the climate.
舆论风向说  我要跨台了
Climate said I was going down.
论风向说  我应该退位
Climate said I should just step aside.
这样说来.
I guess...
我总是逆风翱翔
I'm a climate denier.
不好意思  真的要这样吗
-I'm sorry, this is how it happens?
晚安   -爸
-Good night. Dad?
爸  拜托  他..他很危险
Come on. He's just... he's fucking dangerous.
绝对上床了 [指洛根和凯莉]
Definitely fucking.
你的民调似乎又一次跌落了小西
Looks like your polling was off again, Shiv.
走吧
Let's go.
我昨晚看见你了
So, I saw you.
看来你玩得很痛快
Looked like you were having a whale of a time
借着白男之力飞翔
flying on the wings of white power.
是 是 我被征用了
Yeah. Yeah, I was commandeered.
感觉好吗..
Did it feel good
成为一个法西斯主义升降机
as the fascists hoisted you aloft
像个斯坦利杯
like the Stanley Cup?
所以...
So,
门肯会参加周末的非正式投票
Mencken's gonna take the weekend straw poll
佩特库斯确认他会支持
and Petkus has confirmed he's backing.
好
Good.
周日节目今早播送了他
Sunday show pushed him this morning.
我们看看这匹马能不能跑
Well, let's see if this horse can run.
还是没能...落实下来
Couldn't quite...seal the deal,
现在 我在想
and here I was thinking that
你会成为那个送我爸坐牢的人
you were gonna be the man to put my dad in prison.
是的   -西沃恩
-Right. -Siobhan!
说曹操...
Speak of the devil.
你保重  幸会
You take care. Good to see you.
我们要拍照了
We're doing photos.
全家福   -跟他一起吗
Family photo.  With him?
不拍不拍
No. -No.
我们都要拍  走吧
-We're all in it. Let's go.
画面里人够多了
We've got enough people in the shot.
我就算了
I'm good.
请你前去拍照
Get in the photo, please.
西沃恩  你还是这个家的一份子吗
Siobhan, are you part of this family or not?
不站在他旁边
I'm not standing next to him.
我会拍  但不要站在他旁边
I'll be in the photo, but not right by him.
你赢了  小宝
You win, Pinky. You win.
这周末表现不错  儿子
You did good this weekend, son.
请站在议员身边
-Next to Congressman.
门肯先生   -罗曼
-Mr. Mencken.  -Roman.
恭喜   -谢谢
-Congratulations. -Thank you
好了  大家伙  随意些  放轻松  微笑
Okay, everybody, just be casual. Relax. Smile.
下巴收一下  门肯先...议员
Little chin down, Mr. Mencken. Congressman.
一  二  三
And one, two, three.
很好  很好  完美
Great! Perfect. Thank you.
谢谢  很好
-Good. -Super.
很好  好了
Great. Okay.
谢谢  我们要不要..
Thank you. Should we get...
我们要不要
Should we get a couple of just...